Our Secret
EP16
Astronomy Club.
Welcome to Astronomy Club.
That one.
Music Club sounds good.
It's suitable for you.
That's...
Zhou Siyue
Thank you for the application.
I want to invite you to dinner when you are available.
Come on. Can't let you pay.
It's on me.
I have to go, maybe another day.
Comics Club.
Here, welcome to Astronomy Club.
Welcome to Astronomy Club.
Calligraphy Club.
Just join us!
Excuse me, I can sign up for the Animation Club here?
Yeah, do you wanna come in?
Okay.
Sit down, please.
Ding Xian
You have some drawing experience, right?
Can you show us some previous works?
Okay, here you are.
You are the illustrator,
The Little Monster?
You know me?
I know you for a long time.
You are a gifted illustrator.
It's a surprise for me to be in the same college with you.
I thought you could be a student of an academy of fine arts.
Thank you.
In fact I'm an amateur.
Be confident.
The gift you have
is more important than skills.
Could you tell me
is Zhou Siyue in this club?
Zhou Siyue
If you want to look for him,
this isn't the right place.
Siyue isn't our member,
but a friend in another class.
Comics Club is designing an application
to show our works.
He does a favour for us.
I got it.
Ding Xian
Have you changed your mind?
No.
Come to our meeting on the next Monday.
I'll add you to our group chat later.
Okay.
I found you!
Why you didn't answer my call?
I didn't hear it.
Our counselor is looking for you.
Counselor?
Hurry up.
I gotta go now, bye.
Is the counselor here?
I'm waiting for him.
He hasn't been back yet.
What's the matter with you?
He wants to talk to me
about that thing.
He's kind.
Don't worry.
I have to go.
It's so exaggerating.
We aren't like Song Ziqi and you.
Don't mention him.
I'm angry with him.
Still not reconciled?
I've tried to bring up a topic,
but he didn't reply.
It has been days.
Can you ask Siyue for me
if possible?
Okay, I will try
though I myself haven't found the chance to talk to him.
Seriously?
Ban Jiayu, why did you have your hair done today?
It's time to go!
I'll hang up, Shasha.
I have a party tonight.
Okay.
Hang up, bye.
See you.
Let's go.
You go there in this suit?
Why not?
They are dull-colored.
Really?
I can wear another.
We are here, come on!
Come on!
Here comes our news topic.
You the Huaqing University for love?
Disappointed?
The one you go after is not here today.
It's none of your business.
Okay, all of us are here.
Have a toast.
Welcome our new members.
Thank you.
You've eaten too much.
We have to come back home tomorrow.
Have you finished?
Let's play games.
Okay.
Good.
Have you all played Truth or Dare?
Yes.
Okay, come on.
Wow.
Do you have questions?
Any question for her?
I have many questions for you.
You went away with Zhou Siyue that day,
and what happened after that?
He took me to the playground
and taught me a lesson.
He told me how to
get a first in every subject.
This is Truth or Dare.
You have to tell the truth.
Please obey the rules.
Agree.
Okay, truth or dare.
I choose the dare,
so I don't have to tell the truth.
Okay, it's up to you.
Please do what you did
in front of male dormitory.
We've never seen such a big scene.
Agree.
You are so annoying.
I don't think it's interesting.
The video has been uploaded by others.
If you want,
you can find it online.
Can we continue the game?
Of course yes.
Well,
let me sing a song for you.
That's great.
That's good. Come on.
Sing.
You're a good singer.
Zhou Siyue
I want to study in Jiangling, too.
Bravo.
Okay.
After the game and the song,
do you want to order some other dishes?
I'd like roast trotter.
You're a good diner.
Waiter
Okay.
What a coincidence.
Zhou Siyue
You
are working here?
Yes, a part-time job.
I can help you order dishes.
Here you are.
Your prince charming
looks like a poor childe.
This restaurant is good. I planned to come here long before.
It's pity
that you are on duty
or you can eat with us.
It doesn't matter.
There are signature dishes.
The seafood is transported by air.
Good for party.
Do you like these?
Okay, take your advice.
Okay.
Ask me
if you need.
Uncle Liu, let me do this.
It's okay. I can do this.
I'm sorry to ask you
to change the shift with me.
It doesn't matter.
Come back and look after your kid,
or he will fall sleep.
Okay, thank you.
Zhou Siyue
Why are you still here?
It's a return gift for your treat yesterday.
Anything else?
Did something happen to you?
Nothing.
My father isn't well recently,
so my life is not what it used to be.
I took a part-time job
to help my parents.
Are your parents all right?
Can I help you?
They are fine.
Don't worry about us.
They said you were going to the karaoke.
You have to go now.
You can't turn me away.
Ding Xian
I've told you
that we have our own life.
Now your university life begins. There are lots of
interesting people and things.
You should explore the new life,
don't waste time on me.
I also have a new life.
Embracing a new life means
forgetting the past, right?
The past is the past.
Okay,
I got you.
You finished?
The manager is looking for you.
I'm here.
Here I am, manager.
You wiped the table?
I can tidy it up again.
You don't have to.
You are complained by a guest.
I don't understand.
The guest...
Sometimes their complaints are
totally unprovoked,
but you have to understand me,
catering business is depressed recently.
And he topped up 10000 yuan in his VIP card.
I cannot afford to offend him.
I got it.
Well,
this is my last night here.
I'll leave here tomorrow.
Okay.
Forgive me.
Alright.
Good for you.
You are sweeping the post bar recently.
Are they serious?
These are rumors.
Please,
let me alone.
Okay.
Does someone know the story of
Zhou Siyue, the one majors in computing?
I don't know the details either.
The department told us to keep quiet about it.
It was dealt with in secret.
Only one post left.
You can read it.
Don't judge him if you don't know him.
What do you know about him?
He's a...
He's an excellent man.
Siyue
Come here.
It's too late to have a meal.
No appetite.
Your dad is tired. He's asleep.
My salary of this month.
Why do you get it so early?
It's for my good performance.
You should save a little.
Don't worry. I have scholarship.
It's enough.
You must be tired. You are thinner.
It's not bad.
I look great, right?
Everything will be all right.
Take it easy.
Everything will be okay.
It will be fine.
Hey,
wait for me.
You studied all afternoon.
You can't feel tired?
A lazy man can't understand.
Okay, you are right.
Your GPA is 4.0. I can't compete with you.
You see, there's a post about that girl again.
She is so popular.
You are mentioned, too.
It's none of my business.
Look at this!
Come on.
So beautiful, so sweet.
If she were my girlfriend...
Nice.
It sounds perverted.
The photo is good.
It's taken in front of the bathhouse.
A stalker?
Oh!
You never heard that
a man pestered Xing Lufei
and followed her everywhere
last year.
Then the matter was dropped. We don't know who he is.
He returns to his old trade?
Hey, where are you going?
Back to the lab.
You went there just hours ago!
Yuan Fang the traitor.
How dare you get out alone at night?
You've met so many difficulties.
Why not tell me?
The new life you said
is totally an excuse.
You encouraged me to embrace a better future
only because you were afraid.
Just because of these things,
you want to dump me.
Ding Xian
Have you ever thought over
the relationship between us?
Why should I think over?
It's a simple thing.
There may be some mistakes.
Your friends used to be few.
We two
may be intimate when being deskmates,
so you take our friendship as love.
Four years.
It's been four years, Zhou Siyue.
You reckon that I don't know my own feeling?
I've asked myself for numerous times
if I really like you
or it's just an illusion.
If I can assure myself
of a single thing in the world,
that should be my love to you.
Though you have many friends,
are you sure that
you regard me as a friend but not a lover?
Yes, I am sure.
I don't know you want to
deceive me or yourself.
We all know the truth.
I have to go.
So triggered.
Always beat around the bush.
Why not tell me your true thoughts?
Ask me to figure things out.
I do know my heart.
It's annoying.
In addition,
don't take that tone with me!
Mock at me and pull a face.
Let me guess every day.
Are you dumb?
Speak!
You orator.
Now you are mute like timber!
And you,
don't look at me.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not afraid of you!
Sorry to be rude.
Sorry.
Will you feel too tired
and depressed someday?
What if
that day comes?
I'll help you in any case.
I'll be there for you forever.
Can you take me in?
The boundless sky and endless earth may pass away,
but his vows unfulfilled I'll never forgive.
Men are liars.
I might be crazy to
tell him that.
What should I do next time I meet him?
I don't know what to say.
Stop your complaints.
At least you can see him,
but I don't even know
where Song Ziqi is.
Our stories are tragic.
Ding Xian
I have an idea
to help you and myself.
Okay, I'm listening.
Tell me, why did you move?
I go to work and the hospital every day.
Always come back at midnight
and the gate of dormitory is closed.
So I rent a house
outside school.
What happened to you?
Fought with others.
Me too.
Got a demerit.
I broke up with her.
You see.
I told you we were different.
You two haven't been together seriously yet.
You dare to say that?
Do your parents know that?
I told them and got a scolding from my mom.
You know my dad.
So here I am.
Stay away from them.
And what about Shadi?
We broke up.
Don't fool me.
You've broken up for many times.
It's not a joke.
We are serious this time.
She used to dump me,
but I dumped her this time.
That's my victory.
Come on, don't fib.
What can I do?
I can't tell her these things.
It's okay.
She can find a better boy.
How long do you intend to escape from her?
As long as you will.
Come on.
At sight of injustice with a big roar.
Do it when it's time to go.
They'll make or break your heart and soul.
Hey, hey, yo.
Let me go.
You can ask others.
I want to ask you
about the party
of computing department.
We freshmen want to invite some senior students
to share your experience.
I just want to ask your schedule.
Since you are busy,
I can...
Wait.
I didn't know what you wanted to ask.
I'm free. I can go to the party.
Really?
If you are free,
could you do me another favour?
Many senior students
wanna go to the party
because of Ban Jiayu.
If you want to join us...
I got you.
What can I help you? I'll do everything
for you if I can.
Okay, here he is.
Why did he change the job?
What's wrong with the restaurant?
Don't mention it.
Because of Dong Zhengfei and his gang.
They just went there
to embarrass him.
Dong failed
and lost his temper with Siyue.
He complained to the manager.
It's not bad in fact.
The restaurant is too far from our school.
This one is closer.
Now you arrive.
Remember to add me in the group chat.
Wait up.
What's up?
Could you bring him this?
There are some dishes.
No, he will know it if I go again.
Please, you are so kind.
Hey, man.
Why are you here?
I'm afraid that you're too busy to eat. Here is the meal.
So kind of you.
Yeah.
Okay, you got it.
She's too pitiful
and I can't say no.
But you,
don't deny the tea between you two.
You even know her handwriting.
Is she coming here with you?
She is waiting at the gate.
Like taking photos?
Never appear in front of me.
Thank you.
I didn't know he was tailing me
Here you are.
What's this?
That's an alarm.
Carry it all times to prevent harassment.
You've known him for a long time?
Don't send me away.
I have something to ask you.
Kong Shadi wants to ask you
where's Song Ziqi.
Really?
You still have the mood to worry about others?
You should worry about your own safety.
Your photos are posted online
but you never mind who takes them.
Today he stalked you and took photos of you
and he would do other things to you.
I get it.
Okay.
Come back now.
I'm afraid of being alone.
Zhou Siyue
What's up?
I'm sure that
you are concerned about me.
You're so imaginative.
Can we have a peaceful and frank talk.
Now that you can't escape me,
you can tell me your true thoughts.
Just a moment. Thank you.
I have to go back to work,
so I will stop here.
Okay,
Lou Feng will come to me soon.
Zhou Siyue
why don't you tell me the truth?
Ding Xian
I'll study abroad in the next term.
You'll go abroad?
She entered Huaqing University for you.
I don't mean to poke my nose into your affairs.
As your friend
I could see her efforts to go after you.
Just feel that
she's suffered a lot for you.
I don't want her to go after me.
Well, it's a pity
if you let her go.
You used to be intimate.
If you let her get away, you'll regret.
Try to imagine yourself in my shoes.
I'm not eligible to
start a relationship.
It has nothing to do with
eligibility.
If you fall in love,
why not be together?
It’s easy to say that,
but you are also here to escape your trouble.
It's apples and oranges.
Mine is a special case.
No more excuses.
Don't persuade me. You screwed it.
Are you through?
My words are all good for you.
Just for your own good.
What are you thinking?
Why are you so irritable now?
Then you can stop it.
I don't want to talk about this.
I'm triggered enough.
Little Monster is braver than you.
She never escapes from her feeling directly.
And you don't escape?
Then why are you here?
Okay,
you win.
It's good for you to die alone.
Ding Xian
Come here.
Please give it to Zhou Siyue.
I give it to him?
Yeah, we've asked his favour to
make an application,
and now it needs some changes.
It's inconvenient for you?
Why are you here?
Our president asked me to send it.
Okay.
I got it.
It's too late.
You have to go back soon.
I don't believe the excuse
you gave me last night.
And
I'm not here to force you to date with me.
I don't care.
Zhou Siyue
We love each other.
As I see,
there's no simpler thing than it.
I'll always be with you
no matter how many times you refuse me.
It's my promise.
I found a good fortunetelling book. Let me see yours.
This month is not suitable to start a relationship.
You'd better bide your time
or you'll meet your Waterloo.
Xianxian, or you sit tight.
Haste makes waste.
Stop your nonsense.
I won't help you two
if you talk rubbish again.
Hey, that's not my fault.
The book tells me.
The research group
sounds hard to get in.
Don't to mention the opportunities to go abroad.
I know it's difficult,
but
I can't leave him alone.
He has had many troubles.
I want to make up for my absence in his difficulties.
I can't part with him for these reasons.
What's more, I can make it.
I'll show him my determination.
God doesn't help me
but I can help myself.
Thank you, sir.
This is a freshman.
Siyue
She's from your senior high school.
Do you know her?
The next one.
Hello,
I'm a freshman majoring in computing.
I'm Ding Xian.
Why are you laughing?
Anything interesting?
Why do you want to join us?
I...
Ding Xian
What do you want to do?
I want to go abroad with you.
It's not as easy as you thought.
You would give up many things for it.
You're in the Comics Club.
Do you have enough time to do it?
I can do it.
I'll put much time on it.
You and drawing are both my pursuit.
I'm wondering that
what's your reason to major in computing
though you don't like it?
It's for...
For me.
You've struggled for one year
to gain admission to Huaqing University.
Don't do what you don't like to.
I hope you can think it twice
before you make every decision.
Think of what you like.
I've thought it over.
I've said that I couldn't give you up.
If your reason is going abroad,
I'll go with you.
I can deal with everything for you.
Never mind.
You don't think I can pass the entrance test?
I've never worried about your test.
I know you can do everything
if you want to.
It's no small matter.
As long as you're in the scientific research group,
I won't regret my choice.
I can make it.
Trust me.
So stubborn.